<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Madrid Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="home_title">Choose your Madrid</string>
    <string name="home_info">Whether you’re travelling on a budget or willing to treat yourself to luxury experiences, you’ll find Madrid a fascinating destination. Leisure and cultural options range from admission-free museums to exclusive VIP spots. Madrid is a carefree, unprejudiced city, a favourite with the LGBT community. It also offers a wealth of possibilities to families on holidays, classic travellers or those pursuing the latest trends in alternative fashion, music and art.</string>
    <string name="nav_text_title">Madrid Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="web_link">https://www.esmadrid.com/en</string>
    <string name="c_francisco_title">Basilica of San Francisco El Grande</string>
    <string name="c_francisco_info">This is a monumental basilica in which the paintings by Zurbarán and Goya, as well as its enormous dome, which has the third largest diameter of Christendom, are the main attractions.</string>
    <string name="cat_curches_title">Baroque Churches</string>
    <string name="cat_paseo_title">Paseo del Arte</string>
    <string name="cat_housem_title">House Museums</string>
    <string name="cat_church_title">Baroque Churches</string>
    <string name="paseo_info">This area, known in English as the Art Walk, boasts art and beauty as you’ll see nowhere else in the world.</string>
    <string name="paseo_prado_title">Prado Museum</string>
    <string name="paseo_prado_info">One of the world’s leading art galleries with works by Velázquez, Goya, El Greco, Titian and Rubens.</string>
    <string name="paseo_cibeles_title">Centro Palacio de Cibeles</string>
    <string name="paseo_cibeles_info">This cultural space offers cutting-edge programming and one of the best views of Madrid.</string>
    <string name="house_cerv_title">Cervantes House Museum</string>
    <string name="house_cerv_info">The childhood home of the author of Don Quixote showcases the traditions and customs of the 16th and 17th centuries.</string>
    <string name="house_vega_title">Lope de Vega House Museum</string>
    <string name="house_roman_title">Museum of Romanticism</string>
    <string name="house_vega_info">In the Literary Quarter, this typical seventeenth-century house is where the playwright and poet lived for the last 25 years of his life.</string>
    <string name="house_roman_info">The palace of the Marquis of Matallana, takes us on a trip to Romantic Madrid via its collection of works of art.</string>
    <string name="paseo_title">Paseo del Arte</string>
    <string name="house_title">House Museums</string>
    <string name="church_title">Baroque Churches</string>
    <string name="church_francisco_title">Basilica of San Francisco El Grande</string>
    <string name="church_isidro_title">San Isidro Collegiate Church</string>
    <string name="church_marcos_title">Church of San Marcos</string>
    <string name="church_monserrat_title">Church of Nuestra Señora de Monserrat</string>
    <string name="church_francisco_info">Monumental basilica that stands out for its majestic dome and the decorative paintings of Zurbarán and Goya.</string>
    <string name="church_isidro_info">The grave of San Isidro, patron saint of the city is located in the interior of the old cathedral of Madrid.</string>
    <string name="church_marcos_info">The parish church of San Marcos is a charming little baroque church very near Conde Duque.</string>
    <string name="church_monserrat_info">The church of Our Lady of Montserrat is one of the finest examples of baroque architecture in the city of Madrid and is located in Conde Duque.</string>
    <string name="amus_aquop_title">Aquópolis Villanueva de la Cañada</string>
    <string name="amus_aquop_info">Enjoy Europe\'s biggest water park, with 12 attractions in a beautiful setting near the Navacerrada mountain range.</string>
    <string name="amus_park_title">Amusement Park</string>
    <string name="amus_park_info">The Casa de Campo welcomes you to the most complete recreation centre in Spain, with 48 attractions to suit all tastes and ages.</string>
    <string name="amus_planet_title">Planetarium</string>
    <string name="amus_planet_info">Travel through the starts in the Enrique Tierno Galván park, a stone\'s throw away from the Madrid Río tourist area.</string>
    <string name="amus_zoo_title">Zoo Aquarium</string>
    <string name="amus_zoo_info">The fauna of the five continents at the reach of the visitor in the Casa de Campo.</string>
    <string name="park_capricho_title">Capricho Park</string>
    <string name="park_debod_title">Temple of Debod Gardens</string>
    <string name="park_debod_info">Designed by Manuel Herrero Palacios, this funeral monument was brought stone by stone from Egypt.</string>
    <string name="park_capricho_info">Come visit this lovely park and the bunker that used to house the headquarters of the Republican Army of the Central Region during the Spanish Civil War.</string>
    <string name="park_retiro_title">El Retiro Park</string>
    <string name="park_rio_title">Madrid Río Park</string>
    <string name="park_sabat_title">Sabatini Gardens</string>
    <string name="park_retiro_info">A trip to Madrid is not complete without a walk through Retiro Park, the green lungs of the city.</string>
    <string name="park_rio_info">The green heart of Madrid is a great recreational and cultural area, parallel to the Manzanares and named Madrid Río after the river.</string>
    <string name="park_sabitini_info">Found in the former location of the Royal Palace\'s stables, this quaint park is a wonderful place from which to watch the sun set.</string>
    <string name="art_title">Art and culture</string>
    <string name="amus_title">Amusement Parks and Zoos</string>
    <string name="park_title">Parks and garden</string>
    <string name="amus_park_summary">The Casa de Campo welcomes you to the most complete recreation centre in Spain, with 48 attractions to suit all tastes and ages. There is nothing better to beat stress and boredom than spending a day enjoying what the Amusement Park has to offer. Heart-stopping roller coasters, refreshing dips in Los Rápidos, excitement and thrills, or peaceful walks in nature. With friends or family, fun and smiles are guaranteed.</string>
    <string name="amus_park_loc">Parque Casa de Campo, s/n 28011</string>
    <string name="amus_zoo_summary">Here lies a fascinating world in which the fauna of the five continents can be seen without leaving the city. Elephants, gorillas, exotic and not-so-exotic birds, koalas, dolphins, sharks, giraffes, kangaroos, bears, and animals found on a farm are all found here as well. All the animals of the world are in Madrid. To get to know them, you only need go to the Casa de Campo and enter one of the most important zoos in the world.</string>
    <string name="amus_zoo_loc">ParqueCasa de Campo, s/n 28011</string>
    <string name="amus_planet_summ">Here is a centre to get to know the cosmos and its history. Concerts beneath the stars, exhibitions, and observations under the supervision of experts...All the activities organized by this institution, with its more than 20 years of experience, have a single goal: discovering the universe in a fun way.</string>
    <string name="amus_planet_loc">Avenida del Planetario, 16 28045</string>
    <string name="amus_aquop_summ">This is Europe\'s biggest water park, with 12 attractions and a large green area where visitors can relax or sunbathe. The park is in a beautiful setting with pleasant temperatures and close to the Navacerrada mountain range.</string>
    <string name="amus_aquop_loc">Calle Mirasierra, s/n 28691</string>
    <string name="park_retiro_summ">This green oasis in the centre of Madrid has 125 hectares and is home to over 15,000 trees. From a botanical point of view, the park includes some very important gardens: the Jardín de Vivaces, the Jardines de Cecilio Rodríguez (classical gardens of an Andalusian style), the Jardines del Arquitecto Herrero Palacios, the Rose Garden, and the Parterre Francés with the oldest tree in Madrid, a bald cypress that is believed to be 400 years old.</string>
    <string name="park_retiro_loc">Plaza de la Independencia, 7 28014</string>
    <string name="park_sab_summ">These Classical-style gardens were built in the 1930s on the site of the former stables. Located in front of the north façade of the Royal Palace, the gardens, whose construction began during the Second Republic, were completed after the Civil War.</string>
    <string name="park_sab_loc">Calle Bailén, 22 8013</string>
    <string name="park_cap_summ">Before us is one of the green spaces that make up the natural artistic heritage of Madrid. It is one of the most beautiful and, paradoxically, one of the least known. The Duke and Duchess of Osuna--especially by the Duchess, María Josefa de la Soledad Alonso Pimentel, created it in 1784. As a protector of artists, bullfighters, and intellectuals, the Duchess created an authentic natural paradise frequently visited by the most distinguished personalities of the period, and where the most prestigious artists, gardeners, and set designers worked.</string>
    <string name="park_cap_loc">Paseo Alameda de Osuna, 25 28042</string>
    <string name="park_rio_summ">Madrid Rio is a huge recreational and cultural area both for its landmarks and leisure facilities and the culture it houses, and for being a reference point from which to contemplate and come into contact with monumental Madrid.</string>
    <string name="park_rio_loc">Puente de Segovia, s/n28005</string>
    <string name="park_debod_summ">In 1968, Manuel Herrero Palacios designed these 8 hectares of gardens so that one could sit and admire the magnificence of the Temple of Debod, which had been donated to Spain by the Government of Egypt.</string>
    <string name="park_debod_loc">Calle Ferraz, 1 28008</string>
    <string name="adress">Address</string>
    <string name="paseo_prado_summ">The Prado Museum is the crown jewel of one of the capital’s most visited tourist itineraries: the Paseo del Arte (Art Walk). Its walls are lined with masterpieces from the Spanish, Italian and Flemish schools, including Velázquez’ Las Meninas and Goya’s Third of May, 1808. Its collection comprises 8,600 paintings and over 700 sculptures, so we recommend you decide what you want to see before stepping into the museum.</string>
    <string name="paseo_prado_add">Paseo del Prado, s/n 28014</string>
    <string name="paseo_cib_summ">Located in the Cibeles Palace,  this cultural centre on the Art Walk is the main focus of its activities for the city of Madrid. Its programme revolves around three lines of action: reflection on urban culture, the supply of cultural information, interactive and accessible to citizens and tourists, and, finally, the meeting of  cultures through the holding of exhibitions, workshops, conferences and concerts, among other offerings.</string>
    <string name="paseo_cib_add">Plaza de Cibeles, 1 28014</string>
    <string name="house_roman_summ">Theold palace of the Marquis of Matallana, built in1776, houses an interesting collection of nineteenth century paintings, furniture and decorative art which will give us a better understanding of cultural, political and everyday life in the Madrid of the period.</string>
    <string name="house_roman_add">Calle San Mateo, 13 28004</string>
    <string name="house_vega_summ">The Lope de Vega House Museum, on Calle Cervantes, was built in the sixteenth century and purchased by the great writer of the Spanish Golden Age in 1610. He lived in it until he died, in 1635.</string>
    <string name="house_vega_add">Calle de Cervantes, 11 28014</string>
    <string name="house_cerv_summ">The childhood home of Miguel de Cervantes Saavedra now houses a museum dedicated to this great master of Spanish literature, recreating the customs, traditions, and everyday life of the 16th and 17th centuries.</string>
    <string name="house_cerv_add">Calle Mayor, 48 28801 Alcalá de Henares</string>
    <string name="church_fran_summ">This is a monumental basilica in which the paintings by Zurbarán and Goya, as well as its enormous dome, which has the third largest diameter of Christendom, are the main attractions. This convent complex substituted for the medieval Franciscan monastery. It was built by Francisco de las Cabezas between 1761 and 1768, the year in which it was taken over by Antonio Polo, who closed the dome.</string>
    <string name="church_fran_add">Calle San Buenaventura, 1 28005</string>
    <string name="church_marcos_summ">Its name comes from Philip V of Spain\'s victory in the battle of Almansa on 25th April 1707, San Marcos Day.</string>
    <string name="church_marcos_add">Calle San Leonardo, 10 28015</string>
    <string name="church_mon_summ">It has been many years since the church of Our Lady of Montserrat stopped the tradition of ringing its bells at midnight for the soul of king Philip V. The bells were rung at this time as it was the time that the Benedictine monks heard of the death of their monarch and the founder of the abbey as it then was. The church, in the centre of the Conde Duque district, was on course to be one of the largest and most majestic churches of its time. But it was never completed. You only have to look up to see that. Even the most unobservant will notice that there is only one tower. The other was never built.</string>
    <string name="church_mon_add">Calle San Bernardo, 79 28015</string>
    <string name="church_isidro_summ">It was Madrid’s main cathedral until the completion of the work done on the Almudena Cathedral. Its high altar contains the tomb of San Isidro, the patron saint of the city.</string>
    <string name="church_isidro_add">Calle Toledo, 37 28005</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
</resources>
